Register of the William Patrick Clark papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- United States Department of the Interior File, 1983-1985
  - Speeches and events file
    - Moroccan Embassy reception, Washington, D.C., 1984 July 24 (Box-folder 101: 19)
    - Visit to California, Nevada, Colorado and New Mexico, 1984 July 26-August 5 (Box-folder 102: 1)
    - Pecos National Monument visitor center dedication, New Mexico, 1984 August 5 (Box-folder 102: 2)
    - Visit to North Dakota and Minnesota, 1984 August 11 (Box-folder 102: 3)
    - Press conference, Fargo, North Dakota, 1984 August 11 (Box-folder 102: 4)
    - Visit to California, Nevada and Texas, 1984 August 14-17 (Box-folder 102: 5)
    - Point Sur Light Station transfer, California, 1984 August 16 (Box-folder 102: 6)
    - Rotary Club meeting, Monterey, California, 1984 August 16 (Box-folder 102: 7)
    - Citizens for America meeting, San Diego, California, 1984 August 17 (Box-folder 102: 8)
    - National Counterintelligence Corps Association convention, Las Vegas, Nevada, 1984 August 18 (Box-folder 102: 9)
    - Republican National Convention, Dallas, Texas, 1984 August 20-23 (Box-folder 102: 10)
    - Kiwanis Club district convention, Fresno, California, 1984 August 24 (Box-folder 102: 11)
    - Republican barbecue, San Luis Obispo, California, 1984 August 25 (Box-folder 102: 12)
    - Garrison Diversion Unit Commission meeting, Washington, D.C., 1984 August 30 (Box-folder 102: 13)
    - Visit to New York (canceled), 1984 September 5 (Box-folder 102: 14)
    - National Press Club dinner, Washington, D.C., 1984 September 6 (Box-folder 103: 1, Box-folder 102: 15)
    - Oceans '84 Conference and Exposition, Washington, D.C., 1984 September 10 (Box-folder 103: 2)
    - Republican Hispanic Assembly leadership conference, Washington, D.C., 1984 September 11 (Box-folder 103: 3)
    - U.S. Geological Survey National Center anniversary celebration, Washington, D.C., 1984 September 13 (Box-folder 103: 4)
    - Visit to Texas, New Mexico, Arizona, Wyoming and California, 1984 September 16-23 (Box-folder 104: 1, Box-folder 103: 5-7)
    - Manuel Lujan fundraiser, Albuquerque, New Mexico, 1984 September 17 (Box-folder 104: 2)
    - Visit to Arizona, Colorado and Utah, 1984 September 24-27 (Box-folder 104: 3)
    - American Mining Congress convention, Phoenix, Arizona, 1984 September 24 (Box-folder 104: 4-5)
    - Public Lands Council convention, Denver, Colorado, 1984 September 25 (Box-folder 104: 6)
    - Republican Party dinner, Salt Lake City, Utah, 1984 September 26 (Box-folder 105: 1)
    - Visit to Florida, Spain and Great Britain, 1984 October 6-14 (Box-folder 105: 2-3)
    - Viva '84 reception, Miami, Florida, 1984 October 6 (Box-folder 105: 4)
    - Father Junipero Serra commemoration ceremony, Mallorca, Spain, 1984 October 11 (Box-folder 105: 5)
    - American Bar Association Standing Committee on Law and National Security meeting, Washington, D.C., 1984 October 16 (Box-folder 105: 6)
    - Visit to California, Washington and Oregon, 1984 October 22-27 (Box-folder 106: 1)
    - California Republican Hispanic fundraiser, Los Angeles, California, 1984 October 22 (Box-folder 106: 2)
    - Richard Gomez fundraiser, Los Angeles, California, 1984 October 23 (Box-folder 106: 3)
    - Robert Dornan fundraiser, Newport Beach, California, 1984 October 23 (Box-folder 106: 4)
    - United Anglers of California meeting, San Rafael, California, 1984 October 24 (Box-folder 106: 5)
    - Yakima Project fish passage improvements ceremony, Yakima, Washington, 1984 October 25 (Box-folder 106: 6)
    - Washington Athletic Club luncheon, Seattle, Washington, 1984 October 25 (Box-folder 106: 7)
    - Department of the Interior employees meeting, Portland, Oregon, 1984 October 26 (Box-folder 106: 8)
    - Pacific Logging Congress meeting, Portland, Oregon, 1984 October 26 (Box-folder 106: 9)
    - Visit to California, 1984 October 29-November 2 (Box-folder 106: 10)
    - Comstock Club luncheon, Sacramento, California, 1984 October 30 (Box-folder 106: 11)
    - Kiwanis Club luncheon, Burbank, California, 1984 October 31 (Box-folder 107: 1)
    - Commonwealth Club luncheon, San Francisco, California, 1984 November 1 (Box-folder 107: 2)
    - California Manufacturers Association luncheon, Los Angeles, California, 1984 November 2 (Box-folder 107: 3)
    - Vietnam Veterans Memorial conveyance, Washington, D.C., 1984 November 12 (Box-folder 107: 4)
    - Visit to California, 1984 November 19-December 1 (Box-folder 107: 5)
    - United States Park Police Horsemounted Unit graduation ceremony, Washington, D.C., 1984 December 12 (Box-folder 107: 6)
    - Visit to California, 1984 December 21-1985 January 1 (Box-folder 107: 7)
    - Presidential inaugural activities, Washington, D.C., 1985 January 17-21 (Box-folder 107: 8)
  - Congressional testimony
    Bound volumes of Congressional hearing reports including testimony by Clark
    - Volume 1 (Box-folder 108: 1)
      Includes U.S. Senate Committee on Energy and Natural Resources hearings on nomination of Clark to be Secretary of the Interior, 1983 November 1-2; U.S. House Committee on Interior and Insular Affairs briefing by Clark, 1984 January 25; U.S. Senate Committee on Energy and Natural Resources budget request hearings, 1984 February 7-9
    - Volume 2 (Box-folder 108: 2)
      Includes U.S. Senate Committee on Appropriations hearings on Department of the Interior and related appropriations for FY 1985, 1984 February 24-April 2; U.S. Senate Committee on Appropriations hearings on energy and water development appropriations for FY 1985, 1984 February 9-29
    - Volume 3 (Box-folder 109: 1)
      Includes U.S. House Committee on Appropriations hearings on energy and water development appropriations for FY 1985, 1984 February 27-28; U.S. House Committee on Appropriations hearings on Department of the Interior and related appropriations for FY 1985, 1984 February 2-March 22
    - Volume 4 (Box-folder 109: 2)
      Includes U.S. Senate Committee on Energy and Natural Resources hearings on federal coal leasing, 1984 March 21 and April 5; U.S. House Committee on Appropriations hearings on Department of the Interior and related appropriations for FY 1985, 1984 April 30-June 14
    - Volume 5 (Box-folder 110: 1)
      Includes U.S. House Committee on Interior and Insular Affairs Subcommittee on Public Lands and National Parks hearings on public land management policy, 1984 June 5-25; U.S. Senate Committee on Energy and Natural Resources Subcommittee on Energy Sources and Supply hearings on Outercontinental Shelf leasing activities, 1984 June 26
  - Chronological correspondence (outgoing letters)
    - 1983 November (Box-folder 111: 1)
    - 1983 December (Box-folder 111: 2)
    - 1983 gift lists (Box-folder 111: 3)
    - 1983 gift acknowledgments (Box-folder 111: 4)
    - 1984 correspondence log (Box-folder 111: 5)
    - 1984 January (Box-folder 111: 6)
    - 1984 February (Box-folder 111: 7)
    - 1984 March (Box-folder 111: 8)
    - 1984 April (Box-folder 111: 9)
    - 1984 May (Box-folder 111: 10)
    - 1984 June (Box-folder 111: 11)
    - 1984 July (Box-folder 111: 12)
    - 1984 August (Box-folder 111: 13)
    - 1984 September (Box-folder 111: 14)
    - 1984 October (Box-folder 111: 15)
    - 1984 November (Box-folder 112: 1)
    - 1984 December (Box-folder 112: 2)
    - 1984 gift lists (Box-folder 112: 3)
    - 1984 gift acknowledgments (Box-folder 112: 4)
    - 1985 correspondence log (Box-folder 112: 5)
    - 1985 January (Box-folder 112: 6)
    - 1985 February (Box-folder 112: 7)
    - 1985 gift lists (Box-folder 112: 8)
    - 1985 gift acknowledgments (Box-folder 112: 9)
  - 1983 alphabetical correspondence
    - A (Box-folder 112: 10)
    - Abrams, Elliott (Box-folder 112: 11)
    - Adams, Ansel (Box-folder 112: 12)
    - B (Box-folder 112: 13)
    - Berryman, Jack H. (Box-folder 112: 14)
    - Blair, William D., Jr. (Box-folder 112: 15)
    - Boyd, Alan (Box-folder 112: 16)
    - C (Box-folder 112: 17)
    - Cheney, Richard (Box-folder 112: 18)
    - Crandall, Derrick A. (Box-folder 112: 19)
    - D (Box-folder 113: 1)
    - E (Box-folder 113: 2)
    - F (Box-folder 113: 3)
    - G (Box-folder 113: 4)
    - H (Box-folder 113: 5)
    - Hair, Jay D. (Box-folder 113: 6)
    - Hermes, Peter (West German ambassador) (Box-folder 113: 7)
    - J (Box-folder 113: 8)
    - K (Box-folder 113: 9)
    - L (Box-folder 113: 10)
    - Laxalt, Paul (Box-folder 113: 11)
    - M (Box-folder 113: 12)
    - Meese, Edwin, III (Box-folder 113: 13)
    - Mosk, Stanley (Box-folder 113: 14)
    - N (Box-folder 113: 15)
    - O (Box-folder 113: 16)
    - Orfila, Alejandro (Box-folder 113: 17)
    - P (Box-folder 113: 18)
    - Q (Box-folder 113: 19)
    - R (Box-folder 113: 20)
    - Rockefeller, David (Box-folder 113: 21)
    - S (Box-folder 113: 22)
    - T (Box-folder 113: 23)
    - Thurmond, Strom (Box-folder 113: 24)
    - U (Box-folder 113: 25)
    - V (Box-folder 113: 26)
    - W (Box-folder 113: 27)
    - Weinberger, Caspar (Box-folder 113: 28)
    - Weiss, Seymour (Box-folder 113: 29)
    - Y (Box-folder 113: 30)
    - Z (Box-folder 113: 31)
    - Zhang, Wenjin (Chinese ambassador) (Box-folder 113: 32)
  - 1984 alphabetical correspondence
    - A (Box-folder 113: 33)
    - Abshire, David M. (Box-folder 113: 34)
    - Andrus, Cecil D. (Box-folder 113: 35)
    - Annenberg, Walter H. (Box-folder 113: 36)
    - B (Box-folder 114: 1-2)
    - Baker, Howard H., Jr. (Box-folder 114: 3)
    - Baldrige, Malcolm (Box-folder 114: 4)
    - Birendra Bir Bikram Shah Dev, King of Nepal (Box-folder 113: 5)
    - Block, John R. (Box-folder 114: 6)
    - Botha, Pieter Willem (prime minister of South Africa) (Box-folder 114: 7)
    - Brock, William E. (Box-folder 114: 8)
    - Brooks, Claudia (Box-folder 114: 9)
    - Bush, George (Box-folder 114: 10)
    - C (Box-folder 114: 11-12)
    - Carter, Jimmy (Box-folder 114: 13)
    - Cranston, Alan (Box-folder 114: 14)
    - D (Box-folder 115: 1)
    - Deaver, Michael K. (Box-folder 115: 2)
    - Deukmejian, George (Box-folder 115: 3)
    - Drury, Allen (Box-folder 115: 4)
    - E (Box-folder 115: 5)
    - Edwards, Mickey (Box-folder 115: 6)
    - F (Box-folder 115: 7)
    - Fourie, B. G. (South African ambassador) (Box-folder 115: 8)
    - Franz Joseph II, Prince of Liechtenstein (Box-folder 115: 9)
    - G (Box-folder 115: 10)
    - Garrick, Robert M. (Box-folder 115: 11)
    - Gavin, John (Box-folder 115: 12)
    - Gerson, Allan (Box-folder 115: 13)
    - Gildred, Theodore E. (Box-folder 115: 14)
    - Gingrich, Newt (Box-folder 115: 15)
    - Goldwater, Barry (Box-folder 115: 16)
    - H (Box-folder 115: 17, Box-folder 116: 1)
    - Hair, Jay D. (Box-folder 116: 2)
    - Hermes, Peter (West German ambassador) (Box-folder 116: 3)
    - Hickel, Walter J. (Box-folder 116: 4)
    - Hodel, Donald Paul (Box-folder 116: 5)
    - Hussein, King of Jordan (Box-folder 116: 6)
    - I (Box-folder 116: 7)
    - J (Box-folder 116: 8)
    - K (Box-folder 116: 9)
    - Kane, Robert F. (Box-folder 116: 10)
    - Kirchschlager, Rudolf (president of Austria) (Box-folder 116: 11)
    - Kirkpatrick, Jeane J. (Box-folder 116: 12)
    - Kissinger, Henry A. (Box-folder 116: 13)
    - Klestil, Thomas (Austrian ambassador) (Box-folder 116: 14)
    - Kreisky, Hugo (Box-folder 116: 15)
    - L (Box-folder 116: 16)
    - Lane, L. W., Jr. (Box-folder 116: 17)
    - Laxalt, Paul (Box-folder 116: 18)
    - Lehrman, Lew (Box-folder 116: 19)
    - Livermore, Norman B., Jr. (Box-folder 116: 20)
    - Livermore, Putnam (Box-folder 116: 21)
    - M (Box-folder 117: 1-2)
    - McFarlane, Robert C. (Box-folder 117: 3)
    - Middendorf, J. William, II (Box-folder 117: 4)
    - Mosk, Stanley (Box-folder 117: 5)
    - N (Box-folder 117: 6)
    - Neumann, Robert G. (Box-folder 117: 7)
    - Nixon, Richard M. (Box-folder 117: 8)
    - Nofziger, Lyn (Box-folder 117: 9)
    - O (Box-folder 117: 10)
    - O'Brien, Thomas M. (Box-folder 117: 11)
    - O'Sullivan, Tadhg (Irish ambassador) (Box-folder 117: 12)
    - P (Box-folder 117: 13)
    - Petrignani, Rinaldo (Italian ambassador) (Box-folder 117: 14)
    - Pfaltzgraff, Robert L., Jr. (Box-folder 117: 15)
    - Pritchard, Paul (Box-folder 117: 16)
    - Q (Box-folder 117: 17)
    - R (Box-folder 118: 1)
    - Reagan, Ronald (Box-folder 118: 2)
    - Regan, Donald T. (Box-folder 118: 3)
    - Reich, Otto J. (Box-folder 118: 4)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. (Box-folder 118: 5)
    - Rostropovich, Mstislav (Box-folder 118: 6)
    - S (Box-folder 118: 7-8)
    - Shultz, George P. (Box-folder 118: 9)
    - Smith, William French (Box-folder 118: 10)
    - Stevens, Ted (Box-folder 118: 11)
    - Stockman, David (Box-folder 118: 12)
    - T (Box-folder 118: 13)
    - Taylor, Ted (Box-folder 118: 14)
    - Thapa, Bhekh Bahadur (Nepalese ambassador) (Box-folder 118: 15)
    - Theberge, James D. (Box-folder 119: 1)
    - Train, Russell E. (Box-folder 119: 2)
    - U (Box-folder 119: 3)
    - V (Box-folder 119: 4)
    - Vernier-Palliez, Bernard (French ambassador) (Box-folder 119: 5)
    - Von Damm, Helene (Box-folder 119: 6)
    - W (Box-folder 119: 7)
    - Walker, June G. (Box-folder 119: 8)
    - Weinberger, Caspar (Box-folder 119: 9)
    - Whalen, Richard J. (Box-folder 119: 10)
    - Wick, Charles Z. (Box-folder 119: 11)
    - Wilson, Pete (Box-folder 119: 12)
    - Y (Box-folder 119: 13)
    - Yates, Sidney R. (Box-folder 119: 14)
    - Z (Box-folder 119: 15)
    - Zhang, Wenjin (Chinese ambassador) (Box-folder 119: 16)
  - 1985 alphabetical correspondence
    - A (Box-folder 119: 17)
    - B (Box-folder 119: 18)
    - Baldrige, Malcolm (Box-folder 119: 19)
    - Byrd, Robert C. (Box-folder 119: 20)
    - C (Box-folder 119: 21)
    - Childress, Richard T. (Box-folder 119: 22)
    - D (Box-folder 119: 23)
    - Deukmejian, George (Box-folder 119: 24)
    - E (Box-folder 119: 25)
    - F (Box-folder 119: 26)
    - Feulner, Edwin J., Jr. (Box-folder 119: 27)
    - G (Box-folder 119: 28)
    - Goldwater, Barry (Box-folder 119: 29)
    - H (Box-folder 120: 1)
    - Hatch, Orrin G. (Box-folder 120: 2)
    - Herrington, John S. (Box-folder 120: 3)
    - Hill, A. Alan (Box-folder 120: 4)
    - I (Box-folder 120: 5)
    - J (Box-folder 120: 6)
    - K (Box-folder 120: 7)
    - Kreisky, Bruno (Box-folder 120: 8)
    - L (Box-folder 120: 9)
    - Lalaing, Comte de (Box-folder 120: 10)
    - Lane, L. W., Jr. (Box-folder 120: 11)
    - M (Box-folder 120: 12)
    - Meese, Edwin, III (Box-folder 120: 13)
    - N (Box-folder 120: 14)
    - o (Box-folder 120: 15)
    - O'Sullivan, Tadhg (Irish ambassador) (Box-folder 120: 16)
    - P (Box-folder 120: 17)
    - Pipes, Richard (Box-folder 120: 18)
    - R (Box-folder 120: 19)
    - Regan, Donald T. (Box-folder 120: 20)
    - S (Box-folder 120: 21)
    - Sabah, Saud N. al- (Kuwaiti ambassador) (Box-folder 120: 22)
    - Shultz, George P. (Box-folder 120: 23)
    - Smith, William French (Box-folder 120: 24)
    - T (Box-folder 120: 25)
    - Theberge, James D. (Box-folder 120: 26)
    - U (Box-folder 120: 27)
    - W (Box-folder 120: 28)
    - Watt, James G. (Box-folder 120: 29)
    - Wilson, Pete (Box-folder 120: 30)
    - Winsor, Curtin (Box-folder 120: 31)
    - Y (Box-folder 120: 32)
  - Subject file
    - Acid rain, 1982 (Box-folder 121: 1)
      Memoranda and speech
    - Advisory committees, 1984 (Box-folder 121: 2)
    - Amadeus (Horse), 1984 (Box-folder 121: 3)
    - Aquatrain Project, 1984 (Box-folder 121: 4)
    - Auburn Dam (California), 1984 (Box-folder 121: 5)
    - Buenos Aires Ranch (Arizona), 1984-1985 (Box-folder 121: 6)
      Correspondence, memoranda and clippings re proposed acquisition as wildlife refuge
    - Cabinet councils and working groups, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 121: 7)
      Minutes and memoranda
    - California Polytechnic State University, 1984 (Box-folder 121: 8)
    - Channel Islands National Park (California), 1983 (Box-folder 121: 9)
    - Compound 1080, 1984 (Box-folder 121: 10)
    - El Salvador, 1984 (Box-folder 121: 11)
      Letter and television transcript
    - Environmental concerns, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 121: 12)
      Correspondence, memoranda, statements, notes and clippings
    - Federal coal leasing, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 121: 13)
      Correspondence and press releases
    - Garrison Diversion Unit Commission, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 121: 14, Box-folder 122: 1-2)
      Correspondence, memoranda, reports and printed matter, re a project to divert water from the Missouri River for irrigation and other uses in North Dakota
    - German-American Friendship Garden (Washington, D.C.), 1983-1984 (Box-folder 122: 3)
    - Haig, Alexander, 1984 (Box-folder 122: 4)
      Interview transcript, memoranda, notes and clippings, mainly relating to publication of Haig's memoir Caveat: Realism, Reagan and Foreign Policy
    - Indian reservations, 1984 (Box-folder 122: 5)
      Report of Presidential Commission on Indian Reservation Economies
    - Ireland, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 122: 6)
      Correspondence, memoranda and printed matter
    - McLaughlin, Ann Dore, 1984 (Box-folder 122: 7)
      Speech
    - National Fish and Wildlife Foundation, 1985 (Box-folder 122: 8)
      Memoranda and press release
    - Outdoor recreation resources, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 122: 9, Box-folder 123: 1)
    - Outer Continental Shelf, 1984 (Box-folder 123: 2-4)
      Correspondence, memoranda, judicial decision and printed matter, re oil and gas leasing
    - President's Parkway (Atlanta, Georgia), 1983-1984 (Box-folder 123: 5)
    - President's Commission on Executive Exchange, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 124: 1)
      Minutes and printed matter
    - San Luis Drain (San Joaquin River Valley, California, including Kesterson Reservoir), 1984 (Box-folder 124: 2-4)
    - Serra (Junipero) commemorative postage stamp, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 124: 5)
      Correspondence, memoranda and clippings
    - State of the Union, 1985 (Box-folder 124: 6)
      Memorandum re Presidential address
    - Strategic materials, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 124: 7)
      Report and memorandum
    - Surface mining, 1984 (Box-folder 124: 8)
      Correspondence and press release
    - Susquehanna River Basin Commission, 1984 (Box-folder 124: 9)
      Letter of appointment
    - Sweeney Ridge (California), 1984 (Box-folder 125: 1)
      Correspondence, memoranda and press releases, re acquisition as addition to Golden Gate National Recreation Area
    - United Farm Agency (Oregon), 1984 (Box-folder 125: 2)
      Brochures
    - United States Park Police, 1984 (Box-folder 125: 3)
      Memoranda and manual, re Horsemounted Unit
  - Memoranda and letters by Carol Hallett, 1984 (Box-folder 125: 4)
  - Miscellaneous memoranda re pending and post-election issues, 1984 (Box-folder 125: 5)
  - Department of the Interior press releases
    - 1983 November-December (Box-folder 125: 6)
    - 1984 January (Box-folder 125: 7)
    - 1984 February (Box-folder 125: 8-9)
    - 1984 March-May (Box-folder 126: 1)
    - 1984 June-August (Box-folder 126: 2)
    - 1984 September (Box-folder 126: 3-5)
    - 1984 October-December (Box-folder 126: 6)
    - 1985 January-February (Box-folder 126: 7)
  - Clippings and serial issues, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 127: 1-3)
    Mainly relating to the Reagan administration and environmental issues
  - Miscellany (Box-folder 127: 4)
  - Resignation as Secretary of the Interior, 1985 (Box-folder 127: 5)
    Letter of resignation, letter of acceptance, announcement, personnel documents and press coverage
- Post-Government Service File, 1985-2008
  Papers of Wiliam P. Clark after his retirement from government service in 1985
  - Biographical file
    - General, 1985-2005 (Box-folder 128: 1)
      Biographical directory data, certificates and questionnaire responses
    - Press coverage, 1985-2003 (Box-folder 128: 2)
    - Joan Clark (wife of William P. Clark), 1985-1999 (Box-folder 128: 3)
      Biographical data and correspondence
    - Airplane accident, 1988 (Box-folder 128: 4-5)
      Press coverage and get-well correspondence
    - Medical records, 1985-2001 (Box-folder 128: 6)
    - Tax records, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 129: 1)
    - Travel records, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 129: 2-4)
  - Appointment books
    - 1985 (Box-folder 129: 5)
    - 1986 (Box-folder 129: 6)
    - 1987 (Box-folder 129: 7)
    - 1988 (Box-folder 130: 1)
    - 1989 (Box-folder 130: 2)
    - 1990 (Box-folder 130: 3)
  - Speeches and events
    Correspondence, memoranda, notes, programs, press coverage, speech materials and speeches
    - National Food Processors' Association convention, San Francisco, California, 1985 February 11 (Box-folder 130: 4-5)
    - Interpublic Group of Companies dinner, New York, New York, 1985 February 13 (Box-folder 130: 6)
    - Dinner in honor of Howard H. Baker, Jr., San Luis Obispo, California, 1985 February 22 (Box-folder 130: 7)
    - Department of Defense Distinguished Public Service Medal award to Clark, Washington, D.C., 1985 February 28 (Box-folder 130: 8)
    - Farewell dinner, Washington, D.C., 1985 March 5 (Box-folder 130: 9)
    - Center for Strategic and International Studies Washington Quarterly Roundtable dinner in honor of Clark, Washington, D.C., 1985 March 6 (Box-folder 130: 10)
    - Texas and Southwestern Cattle Raisers' Association convention, Fort Worth, Texas, 1985 March 18 (Box-folder 130: 11)
    - Thacher School commencement, Ojai, California, 1985 June 8 (Box-folder 131: 1)
    - U.S.S. Honolulu commissioning ceremony, Norfolk Naval Station, Virginia, 1985 July 6 (Box-folder 131: 2)
    - American Irish Foundation banquet, Los Angeles, California, 1985 November 14 (Box-folder 131: 3)
    - USA-ROC/ROC-USA Economic Councils joint conference, Orlando, Florida, 1985 November 17-18 (Box-folder 131: 4)
    - USA-ROC Economic Council conference, Taipei, Taiwan, 1986 December 2-5 (Box-folder 131: 5)
    - Asian Business League dinner, Los Angeles, California, 1990 April 26 (Box-folder 131: 6)
    - Respect Life Sunday celebration, St. Rose Church, California, 1995 October 1 (Box-folder 131: 7)
      Includes homily
    - National Wanderer Forum, Washington, D.C., 1995 October 28 (Box-folder 131: 8)
    - Mass celebration, California Polytechnic State University, San Luis Obispo, California, 1996 January 21 (Box-folder 131: 9)
      Includes address
    - Commitment to Life Conference, Long Beach, California, 1997 January 22 (Box-folder 131: 10)
    - Thomas Aquinas College commencement, Santa Paula, California, 1997 June 7 (Box-folder 131: 11)
    - Dinner in honor of Edwin Meese, III, Washington, D.C., 1998 March 26 (Box-folder 132: 1)
    - Human Life International conference, Houston, Texas, 1998 April 15-19 (Box-folder 132: 2)
      Includes speech draft
    - Lincoln Law School of Sacramento commencement, Sacramento, California, 1998 May 17 (Box-folder 132: 3)
    - Hoover Institution/William J. Casey Institute Symposium on the Fall of the Berlin Wall, Washington, D.C., 1999 February 22 (Box-folder 132: 4)
      Includes transcript of remarks
    - U.S.S. Ronald Reagan christening ceremony, Newport News, Virginia, 2001 March 4 (Box-folder 132: 5)
    - Young America's Foundation meeting, Reagan Ranch, Santa Barbara, California, 2002 February 7 (Box-folder 132: 6)
    - Young America's Foundation retreat, Reagan Ranch, Santa Barbara, California, 2004 April 22-25 (Box-folder 132: 7)
  - Miscellaneous speeches and writings
    - "Op-Ed,", 1986 July 1 (Box-folder 132: 8)
      Relates to President's Blue Ribbon Commission on Defense Management. Typescript
    - "High Court Confusion,", 1996 May 10 (Box-folder 132: 9)
      Relates to Supreme Court abortion decisions. Typescript, drafts and correspondence
    - "Natural Law and the Judge's Duty" (letter to the editor), Catholic World Report, 1996 October (Box-folder 132: 10)
      Printed copy